<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Evan&#39;s Notes</title>
    <link>https://evanap.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Evan&#39;s Notes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 11:57:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://evanap.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using awsudo</title>
      <link>https://evanap.com/posts/using-awsudo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 11:57:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evanap.com/posts/using-awsudo/</guid>
      <description>Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been using this tool called awsudo. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple tool that helps you assume roles if you use that strategy in AWS.
Installation Run this command to start the installation:
bash &amp;lt;(curl https://raw.githubusercontent.com/makethunder/awsudo/master/install) Usage If this is your first time using AWS cli, configure your credentials first:
$ aws configure AWS Access Key ID [None]: insert-your-access-key-id AWS Secret Access Key [None]: insert-your-secret-access-key Default region name [None]: ap-southeast-1 Default output format [None]: json Now that you have your credentials configured, you can start using awsudo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vertical Pod Autoscaler Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://evanap.com/posts/vertical-pod-autoscaler-recommendation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evanap.com/posts/vertical-pod-autoscaler-recommendation/</guid>
      <description>Right-sizing a deployment of an app on a Kubernetes clulster is a tricky thing to do. Setting requests and limits too high, you might end up with unschedullable pods due to resource scarcity. Setting requets and limits too low and you might end up with OOMKilled pods. Luckily, there&amp;rsquo;s an answer (kind of) for that. It&amp;rsquo;s the Vertical Pod Autoscaler or VPA for short.
VPA is a custom resource, a part of autoscaling components of Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://evanap.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 18:57:20 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://evanap.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Well, for quite some time I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking to put this personal site of my own. Been stuck in choosing which platform will host this site, whether it&amp;rsquo;s building the platform myself maybe using Docker or some single node Kubernetes cluster, or just a simple web server hosted by a single instance on some cloud. But, the choice comes down to GitHub Pages. It&amp;rsquo;s easy and hassle-free. So, yeah, there&amp;rsquo;s that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>